(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-08-01T16:23:18.434236",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
今日も大天才っ！
I'm a total genius today too!
だーいてんさいいっ！
A total ge-nius!
大優勝っ！
Total victory!
中毒っ！
Addicted!
重症っ！
Critical condition!
今日も大天才っ！
I'm a total genius today too!
だーいてんさいいっ！
A total ge-nius!
あーっ ずっと もっと 推し事させてっね？
Ah~ Let me stan you more and more forever, okay?
アクスタ・痛バ・ぬい 準備万端っ！
Acrylic stands, ita-bags, plushies—all ready!
オシャレも気合い入れちゃって 「誰の為なの〜？」って！
Dressing up with full spirit, going '~Who is this for?'!
惑うことなき 推しの為ですっ！
Without a doubt, it's for my oshi!
古参・新参も 人権は平等
Veterans and newbies have equal human rights,
内に秘めた 古参マウント
With veteran flexing hidden inside.
not同担拒否ですが すこーし嫉妬はするかも…っ！
Not that I reject same-oshi fans, but... I might get a little jealous!
いいね！ボタン 足りません…これ無料でいいんですか…っ！？
The Like button isn't enough... Is this really free...!?
日々好きが募る！尊すぎるでしょ…困っちゃうなあ
My love grows day by day! It's too precious... What'll I do?
今日も大天才っ！
I'm a total genius today too!
だーいてんさいいっ！
A total ge-nius!
推し無シっ！？無理っ！絶対っ！
No oshi!? Impossible! Absolutely!
考える暇もないなあ 生き甲斐
No time to even think, my reason to live!
推し事は年中無休ですっ！
Stanning is year-round without a day off!
もうーっ大天才っ！
Gosh~ total genius!
あーっ限界っ！これ以上供給されたら困ります だって召されそう…っ！
Ah~ limit! If I'm given any more supply I'll be in trouble, cuz I might ascend...!
大天才赦免っ！
Total genius pardon!
あなたがイチバンですっ！
You are number one!
予約した推しのフィギュア “来年発送予定”っ！？
My pre-ordered oshi figure 'Scheduled to ship next year'!?
(マジっ！？)
(Seriously!?)
って、そんなの慣れっこです 忘れた頃に来るけど…っ！
Well, I'm used to that. Though it arrives when I've forgotten...
溢れる祭壇 無論、無限回収ですが…っ！
An overflowing altar. Of course, infinitely collecting, but...!
整理つかぬままに増えすぎるらびゅーっ！
Labyu increasing without being organized!
あーもう！すきっ！
Ah gosh! I love you!
今日も大天才っ！
I'm a total genius today too!
だーいてんさいいっ！
A total ge-nius!
しぬっ！むりっ！まってっ！てえてえ…
I'm dying! No way! Wait! So precious...
考えられないや…尊死…っ！
I can't even think... Dying from cuteness...!
次の現場まで待てないや
I can't wait until the next venue!
もうーっ大天才っ！
Gosh~ total genius!
あーっ限界っ！
Ah~ limit!
今日も大天才っ！だーいてんさいいっ！
I'm a total genius today too! A total ge-nius!
大優勝っ！中毒っ！重症っ！
Total victory! Addicted! Critical condition!
今日も大天才っ！だーいてんさいいっ！
I'm a total genius today too! A total ge-nius!
あーっ ずっと もっと 推し事させてっね？
Ah~ Let me stan you more and more forever, okay?
アクスタ・痛バ・ぬい 準備万端っ！
Acrylic stands, ita-bags, plushies—all ready!
オシャレも気合い入れちゃって 「誰の為なの〜？」って！
Dressing up with full spirit, going '~Who is this for?'!
惑うことなき 推しの為ですっ！
Without a doubt, it's for my oshi!
古参・新参も 人権は平等
Veterans and newbies have equal human rights,
内に秘めた 古参マウント
With veteran flexing hidden inside.
not同担拒否ですが すこーし嫉妬はするかも…っ！
Not that I reject same-oshi fans, but... I might get a little jealous!
いいね！ボタン 足りません…これ無料でいいんですか…っ！？
The Like button isn't enough... Is this really free...!?
日々好きが募る！尊すぎるでしょ…困っちゃうなあ
My love grows day by day! It's too precious... What'll I do?
今日も大天才っ！
I'm a total genius today too!
だーいてんさいいっ！
A total ge-nius!
推し無シっ！？無理っ！絶対っ！
No oshi!? Impossible! Absolutely!
考える暇もないなあ 生き甲斐
No time to even think, my reason to live!
推し事は年中無休ですっ！
Stanning is year-round without a day off!
もうーっ大天才っ！
Gosh~ total genius!
あーっ限界っ！これ以上供給されたら困ります だって召されそう…っ！
Ah~ limit! If I'm given any more supply I'll be in trouble, cuz I might ascend...!
大天才赦免っ！あなたがイチバンですっ！
Total genius pardon! You are number one!
予約した推しのフィギュア “来年発送予定”っ！？
My pre-ordered oshi figure 'Scheduled to ship next year'!?
(マジっ！？)
(Seriously!?)
って、そんなの慣れっこです 忘れた頃に来るけど…っ！
Well, I'm used to that. Though it arrives when I've forgotten...
今日も大天才っ！だーいてんさーいっ！
A total genius today! Absolute genius!
推し事は年中無休ですっ！
Stanning is a year-round job!
今日も大天才っ！
A total genius today!
だーいてんさーいっ！
Absolute genius!
これ以上供給されたら困ります
If I get any more content, I'll be in trouble!
だって召されたら…だって召されない
Because if I ascend... No, I won't ascend yet!
あなたが一番ですっ！
You are number one!
予約した推しのフィギュア
The oshi figure I pre-ordered
“来年発送予定”！？(マジ！？)
is "Scheduled to ship next year"!? (Seriously!?)
ってそんなの慣れっこです
Well, I'm used to that sort of thing.
忘れた頃にくるけど…！
It arrives when you've forgotten all about it...!
溢れる祭壇
An overflowing altar
無論、無限回収ですが…！
Of course, infinite collection, but...!
整理つかぬままに増えすぎるらびゅー！
It piles up faster than I can organize, love you!
あーもう！
Ah, jeez!
すき！
I love you!
今日も大天才っ！だーいてんさーいっ！
A total genius today! Absolute genius!
しぬ！むり！まって！てぇてぇ…考えられないや…
I'm dying! Impossible! Wait! So precious... I can't even think...
尊死…！
Dying from cuteness...!
次の現場まで待てないや
I can't wait until the next live!
もう！大天才っ！だーいてんさーいっ！
Jeez! Total genius! Absolute genius!
切り詰めた生活になひとつ苦じゃないだって
A frugal lifestyle isn't a hardship at all, because
こんなにも幸せ溢れた日々です！
these days are overflowing with so much happiness!
来年も再来年もその先ずっと何年でも
Next year, the year after, and for all the years to come,
推していたい好きでいたい
I want to keep stanning you, keep loving you.
でもあなたの幸せが(yeah！！)いちばん！(yeah！！)
But your happiness (Yeah!!) is number one! (Yeah!!)
無理だけはしないでね？(お願いっ！)
Please don't push yourself too hard, okay? (I'm begging you!)
あなたとあなたを見つけ出した私に“ありがとう”を
To myself, who discovered you and you, I say "Thank you."
今日も大天才っ！だーいてんさーいっ！だーいてんさーいっ！
A total genius today! Absolute genius! Absolute genius!
なんでそんなに大天才っ？困りよ完璧すぎるじゃん
Why are you such a total genius? It's troubling, you're way too perfect!
もう！大天才っ！だーいてんさーいっ！
Jeez! Total genius! Absolute genius!
推しなし！？無理！絶対！考えたくもないなあ…
No oshi!? Impossible! Absolutely not! I don't even want to think about it...
生き甲斐！
My reason for living!
お仕事は年中無休ですっ！もう！大天才っ！
Stanning is a year-round job! Jeez! Total genius!
あー！限界っ！これ以上供給されたら困ります
Ahh! I've reached my limit! If I get any more content, I'll be in trouble,
だって召されたら…だって召されない
because if I ascend... No, I won't ascend yet!
あなたが一番ですっ！
You are number one!
推しに勝るものは無し！
Nothing surpasses my oshi!
これらのこららの始まりは
The beginning of all these things
触れた瞬間アララララ (おはよう！)
was the moment I touched them, alalalara (Good morning!)
ああ、これは困った二度と元に戻れないタイムバースト！
Ah, this is troublesome, I can never go back to how things were, time burst!
そして星が生まれまして
And then a star was born,
アケガタの一番星は (おはよう！)
the morning star at dawn (Good morning!)
あなたと出会った、これは次元を揺るがす大発見
meeting you—this is a dimension-shaking major discovery!
このままハート打ち上げてどこまでも高い空までめっしゃ飛んじゃいたい！
Let's launch our hearts just like this, flying all the way up to the highest sky!
スターダースタート切ったこのラブはあなたに届く？マットなしで大珍生！
Star, star, start! Will this love I've kicked off reach you? A great rare life without a mat!
するぞ！？しちゃうぞ！？あなたに言ってます！
Shall we do it!? We're gonna do it!? I'm telling you!
スターダースタートあのを分かってるほら目の前にずっとあるイントロゼイ！
Star, star, start! Understand that? Look, the intro is right there in front of you!
みてるの？聞いてるの？このビッグバン気づいてーー！！！！
Are you watching? Are you listening? Notice this Big Bang----!!!!
愛は地球クライに膨らんでこんなになってんぞ
Love has swelled to the size of the Earth, and it's gotten this big!
ナナナナナナナナナナナナナナナナ、その時その瞬間のためのスター！
Nana-nana-nana-nana... a star for that very moment!
スターダースタート！
Star, star, start!
電波送信！あなたのハートにノティス！
Radio wave transmission! Notice to your heart!
暇なときでいいよみたいな顔して
Acting like "whenever you're free is fine,"
ちょっとのおんなくれたらよろこばしってかこんなののがすなんてなげかわし
if you give me just a bit of your time, I'd be overjoyed—wait, letting something like this slip by is deplorable!
これらの星の活動は割と続いてモフモフモフモフ
The activities of these stars continue quite a bit, fluffy fluffy fluffy fluffy!
いや！これはすごいな！つまりあなたと私の戸籍！
No! This is amazing! In other words, your family register and mine!
このままハートあなたごと連れて彼方をめざしとれ！めちゃ飛んじゃった！
Let's take you along with our hearts, aiming for the beyond—we flew so far!
スターダースタートこうしたこのラブはあなたに届きゃ今頃超新星してた…
Star, star, start! If this love we started reached you now, we'd be having a supernova...
してたか！ほら今日まで続いた！
Were we!? Look, it's continued until today!
ピュアなスターダースタートちゃんときいてね！一瞬の星って輝くイントロゼイ！
Pure star, star, start! Listen closely! The intro where the momentary star shines!
あなたと！ 私で！
With you, with me!
ピンクモンスター！そうだよ！
Pink Monster! That's right!
ナナナナナナ ナナナナナナナ…
Na na na na na na na na...
愛は地球くらいに膨らんでこんなになってんぞ
Love swells up as big as the Earth!
ナナナナナナ ナナナナナナナ…
Na na na na na na na na...
重なったのはせはこの時のためにさあ スタート！
This moment was made for us, right? Start!
リンドリンド鼓動が鳴り響いて 期待をもっと感じて
Let's feel the rhythm as it echoes!
リリカル Monster
Lyrical Monster!
じょいじょい もっとエンジョイ 今から始まる セーミング
Let's enjoy it more! A thrilling, dazzling feeling!
情緒気分もっと強いホームラン
Your pounding heartbeat is a powerful home run!
脱帽中の才能 ヒヤルキーは 見せてあげる ラブリパピー
Let's show you our shining talent! Lyrical Puppy!
しるるんしるるん 巻き起こるぜデカい台風
Spinning around! An unpredictable hurricane!
もっとハッピー とことんトントン とかげちゃうよ
Let's get even happier, tap, tap, and celebrate!
そうだろう？ころだろう？ときめきだろう？ ラララ リリコでおでかけしましょ！
That's right, Koro-chan! How exciting! One, two, three, go!
そっとビビっと感じたら
Feel that quickening pulse!
止められない止まらないくらい 胸のドキドキドキ ドキ！
My heart is racing so fast I can hardly contain it!
一周回って 現在進行 グルグル追いかけっこ アラララ アラモード
Spinning round and round, chasing after you—alarama mode!
リンドリンド鼓動が鳴り響いて 期待をもっと感じて
Let's ring the bell of our rhythm! Let's feel it even more!
ジャンピジャンピ ディスプレイ おじゃみおさんぽ 気分新世代のライム
Jumping, jumping, display! Let's make this our happy era!
いろはろーは認めません 史上最高の言葉マイスター
We won't accept any ups and downs! This is the ultimate vocabulary!
ユーアンドアイ そこからレディ ずっと見ててでり
You and I, ready from the start, watching all this time!
リリカル Monster さあ行くわ
Lyrical Monster! Let's go!
もっと騒げ ブンブンブーン！そう！それだけじゃないの！大気砲！
Let's make some noise and boom-boom! It's not just about that!
褒めて伸びて うっちょって
Praise us as we soar and flutter!
アベバムバム アベバムバム 天パレバーの鳴いたいふーん
Abe-bam-bam, a typhoon of excitement!
やっぱクレイジー ピシパシピシパシっちゃうよ
Crazy and dashing, let's just go with it!
キミやろう キミやろう グルグルクラブガール おかわり！ いかがですか？
You're cute, let's feel it even more!
もっと愛々しいと感じてよ やめられない目が離せない キミのハッシュタグ！ハック！
Give me more of your attention, I can't stop thinking about your hashtag!
もう一回待って 通常運転のびのび いつも通り アラララ アラカルト
Let's ride the roller coaster again—alarala, alarakuru!
そのままで行くよ リンドリンド 四速は不の 想像以上の初体験
Let's go! Lyrical, lyrical—speed limit is out of the question!
バンピバンピ キスたんもパニッとびしない 発見も買おう
Bumpy, bumpy, kissed and popped, taking off without warning!
孤独中じゃありません 全然絶好の言葉マジシャン
We can't just be lonely! That's totally out of the question, magician!
イエスオーイエス なんでもない 一緒にすぎりりかるなサメディ
Yes or yes, whatever it is, let's do it together! Lyrical Nasamedy!
本当はね リリカちゃんと 二人で歌って踊ってみたいって思ってたんだけどね
Honestly, we both wanted to sing and dance together...
まさかこんな形で叶うなんて！
To think it would actually come true!
誰が一番驚いてるって ジャンケンで決めて！
Who's the most surprised? Let's decide with janken!
日は違う時もあるよ そうそこが良いところ
Even when days are different, as long as it's that place, it's fine, right?
どんな日も笑顔にする 高かさん
Let's make every day full of smiles! Let's go, kids!
どんどん笑って少女コカにこにこ１００万運転 アラララ ラブアップ！
Smile, smile, 1.2 million—alalala, love up!
このまま行くよ まだまだ行くよ ついてきてよね！
Let's keep going, keep going! Stick with us, okay?
リンドリンド みんななら リンドリンド できるはずさ
Lyrical, lyrical, if everyone joins in, anything is possible!
リンドリンド 聞かせて リンドリンド 大きな声で
Lyrical, lyrical, let us hear your loudest voices!
リンドリンド鼓動が鳴り響いて 期待をもっと感じて
Let's feel the rhythm as it echoes! Let's feel it even more!
ジャンピジャンピ ディスプレイ おじゃみゆずるわたしのハッピネスaro
Jumping, jumping, display! Let's make this our happy era!
いろはろーは認めません 史上最高のりの枝から
We won't accept any ups and downs! Let's experience the ultimate lyrical branches!
ましましすーらびす 一緒にしんりりかるなサメディ リリカルモンスターサプライ！
Let's feel it together, lyrical nasamedy, Lyrical Monster's party!
ひざまずきなさい！
Kneel down!
何時？ この城の扉を叩いたものよ
What time? Who is it that knocked on this castle's door?
誓いなさい！
Swear it!
このローナの盾となり矛となり
To become this Luna's shield and spear,
夜はぐっすり眠れるまで
Until you sleep soundly through the night,
側にいること！
Stay by my side!
捧げなさい！ 姫であると
Dedicate yourself, knowing I'm the princess!
守ってルーナイト 大集合！
Protect me, Lunite! Assemble!
何よりもルーナが好きな人
Those who love Luna above all else,
守ってルーナイト 大艦長！
Protect me, Lunite! Grand Captains!
シルクの布団持ってきて
Bring silk futons here!
3時のオヤツ会える人
Those who can meet for 3 o'clock snacks,
守れないカップから即生成！
Instantly generated from unguarded cups!
分かってほしいのだわ…
You need to understand...
これも帝王学を学ぶため
This is also to learn imperial rule,
愛という名の教育なのだわ！
An education in the name of love!
守ってルーナイト お待たせルーナイト
Protect me, Lunite! Sorry to keep you waiting, Lunite!
無駄無駄なボイコットなのだなのだ
Useless, useless boycotts, nanoda nanoda!
背中にチュッ背中越えるのチュッ
Kiss on the back, kiss as we cross backs!
ガラスの靴履かせてワルツ
Waltz with glass slippers put on,
守ってルーナイト お待たせルーナイト
Protect me, Lunite! Sorry to keep you waiting, Lunite!
月曜日にキャンディ足りなくてもね
Even if candy is lacking on Mondays,
君がいなきゃだって見習な
If you're not here, you're just an apprentice!
心して捧げなさい 姫であると
Prepare your hearts and dedicate yourselves, knowing I'm the princess!
ルーナイトお菓子の後ちゃんと歯磨きするの偉い！
Lunites brushing your teeth properly after sweets is amazing!
目覚ましなくたって起きたりしちゃうのすごい！
Waking up without an alarm clock is amazing!
ステップこんがらがっちゃったのも可愛い！
Tangling your steps up is also cute!
今日の褒め言葉よシナノノ
Today's words of praise, shinanono!
守ってルーナイト 大脱走！
Protect me, Lunite! Great breakout!
ルーナ発祥させる人
Lunite instigators!
守ってルーナイト 大劇場！
Protect me, Lunite! Grand theater!
ダイヤモンドの花積んできて
Pick diamond flowers and bring them,
ドラゴンペットにできる人
Those who can make dragons pets,
すべからず言わず即実行！
Without saying anything, execute immediately!
きっとわかってくれるのだわ…
I'm sure you'll understand...
コンシュロンだって読んだのだわ…
I even read Conscience Ron...
恋はいつだってシークレットなのだ！
Love is always a secret, nanoda!
守ってルーナイト 踊ってルーナイト
Protect me, Lunite! Dance, Lunite!
オペラハウス菓子君なのだなのだ
Opera House confectionery lords, nanoda nanoda!
札の整骨 生薬の呪
Bone-setting, herbal medicine curses,
ドレスのバラ咲かせてワルツ
Waltz making dress roses bloom!
守ってルーナイト 分かってルーナイト
Protect me, Lunite! Understand me, Lunite!
バルコニーでモーニングティーに砂糖乗せちゃう
Putting sugar in morning tea on the balcony,
あの人も綺麗だってそんな…そんな…
That person is pretty too, saying such... such...
川ごとはおやめなさい 姫であると
Stop such nonsense, knowing I'm the princess!
守ってルーナイト お待たせルーナイト
Protect me, Lunite! Sorry to keep you waiting, Lunite!
無駄無駄なボイコットなのだなのだ
Useless, useless boycotts, nanoda nanoda!
永久の呪術 生薬の呪
Eternal spells, herbal medicine curses,
ガラスの靴履かせてワルツ
Waltz with glass slippers put on,
守ってルーナイト お待たせルーナイト
Protect me, Lunite! Sorry to keep you waiting, Lunite!
月曜日にキャンディ足りなくてもね
Even if candy is lacking on Mondays,
君がいなきゃだって見習な
If you're not here, you're just an apprentice!
心して捧げなさい 姫であると
Prepare your hearts and dedicate yourselves, knowing I'm the princess!
特者生存ワンダラー!!
Survival of the fittest wanderer!!
行け！はい！はい！はい！はい！
Let's go! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
なぬっ！ビシッ おりゃっ！バシッ ツッコミも冴えて 本日快晴
Nanu! Bishi! Oryah! Bashi! Sharp comebacks, beautiful weather today!
さわっ ボロ… ぎゅ むっ バキッ 手にする全部 it's mine! くれくれ
Sawa... Boro... Gyu, mu... Baki! Everything in hand is mine! Give it here!
適度にがんばろっか (そっか?) そんなんだっていいけどさ
Let's do our best moderately (Really?) That's fine too, but
必死にがんばろっか (そうだ!) それが僕ららしいよな
Let's do our best with all our might (That's right!) That's just like us!
ダサすぎじゃねえんだわ！ そんで貧乏っちいじゃねえんだわ！ うん！万事がバッチリイケてるに決まってる！
It's not uncool! And it's not cheap either! Yeah! Everything's bound to be perfectly cool!
(are you?) かなたちゃん
(Are you?) Kanata-chan!
どどん！前進上等！ちゃんと歓迎して 高まれ
Dodon! Forward advance is top-tier! Welcome it properly, raise the spirit!
海空創造 ちゃんと驚嘆して 興奮しよう
Creating sea and sky, marvel at it properly, let's get excited!
なにっ!? ビシッ おりゃっ!! バシッ
What?! Bam! Take this!! Whack!
ツッコミも咎めて 本日快晴
Even the retorts are forgiven, it's clear skies today!
さぁっ ボロ… ぎゅ むっ バキッ
Now, tattered... squeeze, hum, crack!
手にする全部 it’s mine! くれくれ
Everything I get is mine! Give it, give it!
適度にがんばろっか (そっか?)
Let's do our best in moderation (Really?)
そんなんだっていいけどさ
Anything goes, but you know,
必死にがんばろっか (そうだ!)
Let's work desperately hard (That's right!)
それが僕ららしいよな
That's just so us, right?
ダサすぎじねえんだわ!
It's not too uncool at all!
そんで貧乏っちいじねえんだわ!
And it's not cheap or petty either!
うん! 万事がパッチリ イケてるに決まってる!
Yeah! Everything is spot on, bound to be cool!
(are you?) かなたちゃん☆
(Are you?) Kanata-chan☆
どうん! 前進上等! ちゃんと歓迎して (wonder-la-der-la) 高まれ
Boom! Advance is top-tier! Welcome us properly (wonder-la-der-la), rise up!
海空創造 ちゃんと驚嘆して (wonder-la-der-la) 興奮しようぜ
Creating sea and sky, gasp in wonder (wonder-la-der-la), let's get excited!
ボクが言うんだもん 実際にするんだもん 現実超えろ未来 あーっ!
I'm telling you, I'll really make it happen, transcend reality into the future, ah!
弱点も平気 スイッチでランチァー! (wonder-la-der-la)
Even weaknesses are fine, launch with a switch! (wonder-la-der-la)
すなわち特者生存ワンダランダday (wonder-la-der-la) 楽しもう
In other words, Survival of the Fittest Wanderer Day (wonder-la-der-la), let's enjoy it!
面白がれること 探しだまえ、over? 返事聞かせてくれ!
Seek out things to have fun with, over? Let me hear your reply!
左右なんかじゃない (かなたーん!)
It's not about left or right (Kanata-n!)
決めつけて一直線 (かなたーん!)
Determined straight ahead (Kanata-n!)
つまり企んだら 発射オライだ
Meaning once we plan it, launch is all clear,
ワクワクすんぜ! しゃー!
We're getting excited! Yeah!
「聞いて!!」「推しイベきちゃあああ アイドルオタク楽しい〜! でも」
"Listen!!" "My oshi event is here! Idol otaku life is so fun! But..."
「ガチ※※の結婚は立ち直ってません」「ガチャだ!! 出るまで回せば100%ピックアップ!!」
"I'm still not over their real marriage." "It's gacha!! Spin until you get it 100% pickup!!"
「ｗｗｗｗ 天井でーす ｗｗｗｗ」「何だよそんなこと言っちゃだめだ、おばこ!」
"LOL, hit pity." "Why'd you have to say that, kiddo!"
「うわっすごい! ありがちょー」
"Woah, amazing! Thanks a lot~"
日々これ騒然で go my way!
Every day is chaotic like this, go my way!
虎視眈々でいたいんだもん
I want to keep a vigilant eye out,
だって意気ガンガンがいいんだもん
Because high spirit is what I want,
全方位にがっちり アンテナ張ってないくちゃ!
Gotta keep antennas up tight in all directions!
いつでも心はちゃんと純粋で (wonder-la-der-la) いたいな
Always wanting my heart to be pure (wonder-la-der-la),
好奇心は絶えず熱心で (wonder-la-der-la) いたいなって
And my curiosity passionately eager (wonder-la-der-la)!
言い聞かせるんだ 調子に乗ったら すぐ飽きられちゃうから あーっ!
I tell myself, if I get carried away, I'll get bored of it right away, ah!
タイトなロープも どんどこい でっせ (wonder-la-der-la)
Bring on the tight rope too (wonder-la-der-la)!
すなわち特者生存ワンダランダday (wonder-la-der-la) しがみつけ
In other words, Survival of the Fittest Wanderer Day (wonder-la-der-la), hold on tight!
“努力とは最後まで諦めないこと” メモっておいて!
"Effort means never giving up till the end" — make a note of it!
ホントはbaby 自信ないんだよ
Honestly, baby, I have no confidence,
ホントはbaby 不安ばっかで泣きそうだ
Honestly, baby, I'm full of anxiety and feel like crying,
でもねbaby 挫けないって決めたの
But hey, baby, I decided not to break down,
だからbaby 挑戦したいよ 未開の天地 無限のフィールドで!
So baby, I want to challenge uncharted territories in an infinite field!
前進上等! ちゃんと歓迎して (wonder-la-der-la) 高まれ
Advance is top-tier! Welcome us properly (wonder-la-der-la), rise up!
海空創造 ちゃんと驚嘆して (wonder-la-der-la) 興奮しようぜ
Creating sea and sky, gasp in wonder (wonder-la-der-la), let's get excited!
ボクが言うんだもん 実際にするんだもん 現実超えろ未来 あーっ!
I'm telling you, I'll really make it happen, transcend reality into the future, ah!
弱点も平気 スイッチでランチァー! (wonder-la-der-la)
Even weaknesses are fine, launch with a switch! (wonder-la-der-la)
すなわち特者生存ワンダランダday (wonder-la-der-la) 楽しもう
In other words, Survival of the Fittest Wanderer Day (wonder-la-der-la), let's enjoy it!
面白がれること 探し放題でっせ 無限のフィールドで
Endless things to find amusing in an infinite field,
パンピングしなくてもいい (かなたーん!)
Pumping isn't even necessary (Kanata-n!)
ど真ん中 一直線 (かなたーん!)
Dead center, straight ahead (Kanata-n!)
つまりこれが僕の答えなんだ
Meaning this is my answer!
胸を張れ! 今を生きるその意味を
Stick your chest out! The meaning of living in the present,
輝く日も 輝く輝く日も 確かめ進め!
The shining days, the brilliant, brilliant days—verify and move forward!
おおりゃー!
Let's go!
なにっ!? ビシッ おりゃっ!! バシッ
What?! Bam! Take this!! Whack!
ツッコミも咎めて 本日快晴
Even the retorts are forgiven, it's clear skies today!
さぁっ ボロ…
Now, tattered...
ぎゅ むっ バキッ 手にする全部 it's mine!
squeeze, hum, crack! Everything I get is mine!
くれくれ 適度にがんばろっか
Give it, let's do our best in moderation
(そっか?) そんなんだっていいけどさ
(Really?) Anything goes, but you know,
必死にがんばろっか (そうだ!)
Let's work desperately hard (That's right!)
それが僕ららしいよな
That's just so us, right?
ダサすぎじねえんだわ!
It's not too uncool at all!
そんで貧乏っちいじねえんだわ!
And it's not cheap or petty either!
うん! 万事がパッチリ イケてるに決まってる!
Yeah! Everything is spot on, bound to be cool!
(are you?) かなたちゃん☆
(Are you?) Kanata-chan☆
どうん! 前進上等! ちゃんと歓迎して (wonder-la-der-la) 高まれ
Boom! Advance is top-tier! Welcome us properly (wonder-la-der-la), rise up!
海空創造 ちゃんと驚嘆して (wonder-la-der-la) 興奮しようぜ
Creating sea and sky, gasp in wonder (wonder-la-der-la), let's get excited!
ボクが言うんだもん 実際にするんだもん 現実超えろ未来 あーっ!
I'm telling you, I'll really make it happen, transcend reality into the future, ah!
弱点も平気 スイッチでランチァー! (wonder-la-der-la)
Even weaknesses are fine, launch with a switch! (wonder-la-der-la)
すなわち特者生存ワンダランダday (wonder-la-der-la) 楽しもう
In other words, Survival of the Fittest Wanderer Day (wonder-la-der-la), let's enjoy it!
面白がれること 探しだまえ、over? 返事聞かせてくれ!
Seek out things to have fun with, over? Let me hear your reply!
左右なんかじゃない (かなたーん!)
It's not about left or right (Kanata-n!)
決めつけて一直線 (かなたーん!)
Determined straight ahead (Kanata-n!)
つまり企んだら 発射オライだ
Meaning once we plan it, launch is all clear,
ワクワクすんぜ! しゃー!
We're getting excited! Yeah!
日々これ騒然で go my way!
Every day is chaotic like this, go my way!
虎視眈々でいたいんだもん
I want to keep a vigilant eye out,
だって意気ガンガンがいいんだもん
Because high spirit is what I want,
全方位にがっちり アンテナ張ってないくちゃ!
Gotta keep antennas up tight in all directions!
いつでも心はちゃんと純粋で (wonder-la-der-la) いたいな
Always wanting my heart to be pure (wonder-la-der-la),
好奇心は絶えず熱心で (wonder-la-der-la) いたいなって
And my curiosity passionately eager (wonder-la-der-la)!
はーい、できたー! ありがとうー! ありがとう!
Yay, we did it! Thank you! Thank you!
はい、というわけで皆さん! 一条莉々華生誕祭ライブ2025にお越し下さりありがとうございます!
Yes, so everyone! Thank you so much for coming to the Ichijou Ririka Birthday Live 2025!
ありがとうございます!
Thank you so much!
Thank you!
ありがとうございます!
今日はなんともう一人ね、一緒に出てくれているので、虫を見たいと思います。
Today, since we have another person joining us, let's bring them out!
ゲスト先パイ! (イエーイ!)
Guest senpai! (Yay!)
猫又おかゆ誕生日おめでとう! (ありがとう! ありがとう!)
Happy birthday Nekomata Okayu! (Thank you! Thank you!)
行き止まっちゃった、どこ?
I hit a dead end, where?
あ、ここか、真ん中だ!
Ah, here, right in the middle!
ありがとうございまーす!
Thank you very much!
やったーめっちゃ嬉しいです!
Yay, I'm so happy!
聞いてくれてありがとう! ありがとう!
Thanks for listening! Thank you!
じゃあちょっと自己紹介させていただいてもよろしいですか?
Can we take a moment to introduce ourselves?
もちろん!
Of course!
やったー! 本日の主役、可愛いポジティブ天才の、一条莉々華だよー! イエーイ!
Yay! Today's main character, the cute, positive genius Ichijou Ririka! Yay!
イエーイ! おとなになりました!
Yay! I've become an adult!
いやなんかセクシーさに磨きがかかったことじゃないの?
Wait, hasn't your sexiness been getting even more polished?
ムチムチです。ムチムチです! かわいい!
Chubby. Plump! Cute!
そんなになに？
What's with that?
じゃあ先輩方たちも自己紹介お願いします!
Then seniors, please introduce yourselves too!
はい! 天音かなた、キャッチコピーは筋力50kg、ギュッギュッ握り潰すぞ、ホロライブ4期生かなたんこと天音かなたです!
Yes! Amane Kanata, catchphrase: 50kg muscle strength, squeezing you tight, Hololive 4th Gen Kanatan, Amane Kanata!
かわいい! イエーイ! ギュッギュッ!
Cute! Yay! Squeeze squeeze!
ギュッ! ギュッ! せーの!
Squeeze! Squeeze! Ready, set!
はい、みんなこんおかゆ! ホロライブのズッ友、天才の、最高にイイ声よりだよー!
Hi everyone, Konokayu! Hololive's best friend, genius, with the best voice, Okayu here!
私に足がない取られる! 待って待って、誕生日なのに奪っちゃった!
My legs are gone, they're being taken! Wait, wait, it's my birthday yet you stole it!
皆さんありがとうございます！
Everyone, thank you so much!
あれ？
Huh?
なんか、変な動きしてる人います？
Is someone moving weirdly over there?
だって、面白いから
Because it's funny,
こうやって、こうやって…
like this, like this...
両方にいるからね、両方に
Because they're on both sides, on both sides.
ありがとう
Thank you.
リリカはね、ありがとう
Ririka is like, thank you.
早速ね、そのライブスタートしたわけなんですが
So the live stream has started,
今回の配信のハッシュタグ、右上の方のこちら！こちら！ハッシュタグ、一条リリカ生誕祭2025となってます！
the hashtag for today's stream is #IchijoRirikaBirthday2025!
Xでたくさんたくさんポストしてくれると嬉しいです！
We'd be so happy if you post lots on X!
嬉しいです！
We'd be so happy!
スクショとか感想とか、モリモリ待ってます！
We're eagerly waiting for screenshots and impressions!
モリモリ待ってるからね！モリモリ！
We're waiting eagerly! Eagerly!
ということでね、まずかなた先輩と特者制服ワンダーだ！
So first, Kanata-senpai and the special student council wonder!
イェーイ！
Yay!
ダンスいただきました、ありがとうございます！
Thanks for the dance!
いやもう、この曲本当に可愛くて、踊りもめっちゃね可愛いし、嬉しい！
This song is really cute, and the dance is so cute too!
こうやってね！
Like this!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
いやもうめちゃくちゃ歌えて踊れて嬉しかったで、私たちこそリリカのプロデュースでね
It was so great being able to sing and dance to this.
聞いて踊ってもらえて
We're so glad to be produced by Ririka
本当に幸せでした、ありがとうございます！
We were truly happy, thank you!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you very much!
やったー！
Yay!
そしてこの後ですね、こよちゃん先輩はあの曲を…あの曲！
And after this, Koyori-senpai's favorite song... that song!
え、ダンスできるのあの曲なんだの？どれだどれだ、あれか？
Wait, can you dance to that song? Which one?
もう、リリカの大好きな曲で、
It's Ririka's most favorite song,
本当に？
Really?
あれ、ちょっとおかしい？
Wait, something's weird?
なんか赤くね？赤くなってる！
Why is it red? It's turning red!
え、大丈夫？なんか出てくる？
Eh, is it okay? Something's coming out?
終わって！歌わせて！やばいやばいやばい、何匹いるの！？
Stop! Let me sing! Oh no, how many are there!?
え、何匹いるの！？
Eh, how many are there!?
やばいやばいやばい！
Oh no, oh no!
え！？
Eh!?
やばい、いけ！リリカ！
Oh no, go! Ririka!
いけリリカ、リリカ、いけリリカ！逃げろ、逃げろ、やばいぞ！
Go Ririka! Run away, this is bad!
めっちゃ来てる、めっちゃ来てんだよ！逃げろ！
They're coming like crazy! Run!
ああー！
Ahhh!
なんだ、これ！？
What is this!?
やばい！
Oh no!
え、どうなってるの？リリカ！
Eh, what's going on, Ririka!?
まだ、ちょっとあの…待ってください！
Wait, hold on a second!
あそこに、ゾンビ撃退クリームがある！
Over there, there's zombie repellent cream!
1人で行きましょう！
Let's go get it!
ソフトクリームでしょ？
Soft serve ice cream, right?
違います！これは、幻のクリームですよ！
No! This is a phantom cream!
説明役の楽しみ取ってっちゃダメでしょ！
You shouldn't take away the explainer's fun!
これをゾンビに当てれば、多分ゾンビを殲滅できるはず…！
If we apply this to the zombies, we can defeat them...!
撃退できるはず！
We should be able to repel them!
行け行け！
Go, go!
生徒会のシアターに！
To the student council theater!
リリカ、見てろ！やっつけたれ！
Ririka, watch this! Take them down!
え、あ、どっさりなんだ！
Oh, there's a lot of them!
あ、一撃で当てて！
Oh, hit them in one stroke!
え、ちょっと待って！
Eh, wait a minute!
やばい、やばい、やばい、リリカが！リリカが！
Oh no, Ririka is! Ririka is getting caught!
あ、大丈夫？
Ah, are you okay?
やられちゃった
I got got.
危ない危ない、なんか一瞬のスキを突かれたけどさ
That was close, I got caught for a second there.
ノットリは完了ということで
The takeover is complete.
よかった
Good.
ノットリって、ノードンビ？
Takeover? No-zombie?
ノットリって、ノットリって何だよ！
Takeover? What do you mean takeover!
ノットリ、ハズレじゃないよ
It's not a miss.
大丈夫です！ほら！乗っ取って帰ってきた！
It's okay! Look, taken over and came back!
よかったー！
I'm so glad!
なんなんだこの、まったく分からなかったぞ
What on earth was this, I had no idea at all.
一体何だったんだよ、リリカ！
What on earth was that, Ririka!
いや、実はですね、あの、ちょっとお化け屋敷感みたいなのをせっかく遊園地だから味わってほしいなって思って
Well, I wanted you to experience a bit of a haunted house vibe.
えー！？
Eh!?
まじで！？いや、ジェットコースターが良かった
Seriously!? No, a rollercoaster would have been better.
ジェットコースターだとお化け屋敷感ないな
A rollercoaster doesn't feel like a haunted house.
いや、でも、あの、スモークは炊いてほしいって言ったんですけど
Well, I asked for smoke to be used,
ちょ まさかゾンビまで出てくるとは思わなくて
I didn't expect zombies to come out.
重すぎるだろ！
That's too heavy!
あんたの説明の仕方もおかしかったぞ！
Your way of explaining was weird too!
ゾンビ撃退クリームが最初だったよな
It was zombie repellent cream at first, right?
やっぱパレード…ま、いっか、楽しかったな！
Oh well, it was fun!
おっとということでですね、まあこの後はお姉ちゃん先輩と歌わせてもらいつつ、この状態で送りするんですけど
Alright, so after this, we'll have big sister senpai sing with us!
どういう心境でやればいいんだ、この格好は
What state of mind should I have in this outfit?
出ましたすでにね
It's already out there.
かなた先輩、この後もちょっとここの遊園地でまったりゆっくりしてってくださいな
Kanata-senpai, please relax here in the amusement park afterwards.
一人ぼっちで楽しんで、ふざけんな
Enjoying it all alone, are you kidding me?
行ってきます！
See you!
まったりで歌おうね、嘘でしょ
Let's sing leisurely, no way.
え、一人ぼっち？
Eh, all alone?
僕一人にさせられてんだが
They left me all alone.
もう君の心チクっとしてしちゃえ
Another heart of yours, just go ahead and prick it!
わおーん！
Awooo!
「絶対無理」思い出しちゃうし
We think "that's totally impossible"
だってだって不安になるし
Because we get anxious.
全然嘘つけないし
And we can't tell lies at all.
だってだってバカ真っ直ぐだし
Because we're dead honest.
目指すキラキラきっとぼく次第だ
The sparkling goal depends entirely on me.
ビター？ギブアップなんて言わないんだから
Bitter? We won't say things like "give up."
じっとしてらんないし
We can't just stay still.
だってだって動いちゃう足
Because our feet start moving.
1, 1, ステップアップ
1, 1, step up!
ちょっとずつ進めば夢の式解けちゃうな
Advance a bit and dream formulas unravel.
なりたいぼくをきみが好きなぼくを
The me I want to be, the me you love,
ちゃんと余りなく魅せたいの
I want to show you fully without holding back.
あっちゃっちゃ びっくりするほどできないじゃん
Oof, I can't even do it to a surprising degree.
間違って悩んだりばっかりじゃん
Just making mistakes and worrying.
けどきみに見つけてほしくて
But I want you to find me,
ぼくはきみを迎えに行くんだ
So I'm going to go welcome you.
出会えたならハッピー
If we could meet, it's happy!
あっちゃっちゃ びっくりするほどできないじゃん
Oof, I can't even do it to a surprising degree.
間違って悩んだりばっかりじゃん
Just making mistakes and worrying.
けどきみに見つけてほしくて
But I want you to find me.
見つけて欲しくて 僕は君を迎えに行くんだ
I want you to find me, so I'm coming to pick you up!
出会えたなら ハッピー WAO!! おふざけ全開で！
If we meet, it's happy! WAO!! With full-on silliness!
泣いて泣いて 愛して 尻尾振って
Crying, crying, loving, wagging my tail
WAO!! おふざけ全開で！
WAO!! With full-on silliness!
ダメな僕はどうか 覚えておいて
Please remember useless old me
もう君のこと きゅっしちゃえ！
I'll just squeeze you tight!
もうどうしようとか たまに忘れちゃって沈んだり
Sometimes I forget what to do and get depressed
あんまりいけるかも ふたり 段々じゃってまたダウン
Maybe we can do it, the two of us? Step by step, then down
ふわり ぱんっって 段々じゃってまたダウン
Softly, pop! Step by step, then down
ベッタリがやめられない
I can't stop being clingy
おすわりって それなんだっけ？！
Sit? What was that again?!
ふっかりがとめられない
I can't stop feeling fluffy
また歩いて ボーンにあたるの
Walking again and hitting bone
ワオワオステップ ばぶ死んだふりしてるの
Wao Wao Step, acting like a dead baby
やめてはい！こっちおいで！
Stop it! Hey, come over here!
欲しがる君と あぎすぎな僕とで もっといける気がしています
With a needy you and an over-eager me, I feel like we can go further
あっ、ちょっ、びっくりするほどできないじゃん
Ah, wait, I'm surprisingly incompetent!
間違って悩んだりばっかりじゃん
Just making mistakes and worrying!
君を見つけて欲しくて 僕は君を迎えに行くんだ
I want you to find me, so I'm coming to pick you up
出会えたなら ハッピー WAO!! おふざけ全開で！
If we meet, it's happy! WAO!! With full-on silliness!
だって やっぱり一人じゃダメだけど
Because, after all, being alone is no good, but
集まってバカしてワオっちゃえば
If we get together, act silly, and go WAO!
ほら いつでも言える おかえり！
Look, whenever you can say "welcome back!"
僕は君に伝えたいんだ 大いなる ハッピー
I want to tell you, a grand happy
WAO!! おふざけ全開で！
WAO!! With full-on silliness!
泣いて泣いて 愛して 尻尾振って
Crying, crying, loving, wagging my tail
WAO!! おふざけ全開で！
WAO!! With full-on silliness!
ダメな僕はどうか 覚えておいて
Please remember useless old me
目指すキラキラのきっと僕次第の ピカピカのなんてものじゃないんだからさ
Aiming for something sparkling, surely depending on me, not just shiny
メラメラでブッちぎれ 知らないです はぐれずに競えダイ爆走
Blazing through, I don't know, racing without straying, giant explosion run
君のこときゅっしちゃえ！いいじゃん ハッピーじゃん
I'll just squeeze you tight! It's fine, it's happy!
君の心きゅっしちゃえ！いいじゃん ハッピーじゃん
I'll just squeeze your heart tight! It's fine, it's happy!
聞かせて
Let me hear it
さあ 爪を磨いたら
Come on, once you've sharpened your claws
まだ子供のようなあなたのために
For you who are still like a child
あー 試されたいなら
Ah, if you want to be tested
その愚かな手に手錠をかけて
Put handcuffs on those foolish hands
常世の闇に囚われたまま
Trapped in the darkness of the eternal world
甘い甘いガムを噛んでた
I was chewing on sweet, sweet gum
いくつもの後悔を捧げて
Offering up many regrets
さあ さげて
Come on, lower it
さりげない合図に隠れた
Hidden in a casual signal
答えはすぐにわからせてあげる
I'll make you understand the answer immediately
微笑みな嘘にまみれた
Covered in smiling lies
拒んだままに 受け入れてあげる
I'll accept it while refusing
ほら 悲鳴を聞かせて
Come on, let me hear your scream
さあ 指を鳴らしたら
Come on, once you've snapped your fingers
この子猫のような私のために
For my sake, like this kitten
あー 喉が渇いたわ
Ah, I'm thirsty
薄紅の口に指を散らして
Scatter your fingers on thin crimson lips
狭い牢獄に閉じ込めたまま
Do you want to be kept in a narrow cell
首輪に繋がれたいの？
And tied to a collar?
くだらないルールじゃ奪えない
Unattainable by trivial rules
自由はすでにこの手の中にある
Freedom is already in these hands
愛情では測れない
Cannot be measured by love
弱くなったまま選ばせてあげる
I'll let you choose while you're weak
ほら 心を開いて
Come on, open your heart
わからないふりをして 寝ぼけてるの？
Are you pretending not to understand and acting sleepy?
もっと熱い闇を見せて？ねえ？
Show me a hotter darkness? Okay?
さりげない合図に隠れた
Hidden in a casual signal
答えはすぐにわからせてあげる
I'll make you understand the answer immediately
微笑みな嘘にまみれた
Covered in smiling lies
拒んだままに 受け入れてあげる
I'll accept it while refusing
常世の闇に刻むこの名を知らしめてあげる
I'll make you know this name engraved in the darkness
ほら 悲鳴を聞かせてよ 夢見ないで
Come on, let me hear your scream, don't dream
ほら 聞かせてよ 夢見ないで
Come on, let me hear it, don't dream
ほら 聞かせて
Come on, let me hear it
白黒のジグザグ階段で面倒くささを押さえられてる
"Held back by the troublesome black and white zig-zag stairs,"
何から何まで
from this to that.
しごおわやめてまとめ役なら
If you quit work and play the coordinator,
効くお嬢ずにうなづき合ってる
you're nodding along to the effective young lady.
仲良し小良しで
All buddy-buddy,
さあ だだだだだまれ黙って前よ
now, shut up, shut up, look forward!
言えないね そんな強い言葉は
I can't say such strong words,
少しだけ静かにして欲しいね ああ
I want you to be a little quiet, ah.
私達大望へ
Toward our grand ambition,
世界 てててててぶくややや 果たすその日まで
until the day we achieve it across the world,
レルレルレ獄 やややや あなたの周りも よよよよ
rel-rel-re hell, ya-ya-ya, and around you too, yo-yo-yo,
理解 せせせせ 服あれあれあれ
understand, uniform, ah-ah-ah,
約束の地まで
to the promised land.
さあ掲げよ バテン バテン てててててぶく やややや
Now raise it up, batten, batten, gloves, ya-ya-ya,
今日も議題そちのけだね 嫌になるから私一人でもやっておきますね
Today's topic is brushed aside, it's annoying, so I'll do it even if I'm alone.
全て全て全て任せて それをさせてよ 大事なことなの分かっているでしょう
Leave everything, everything, everything to me, let me do it, you know it's important.
白黒のジグザグ階段面倒くさいまま
With the annoying black and white zig-zag stairs,
今日も明日も過ぎていくのでしょう
today and tomorrow will probably just pass by.
花瓶に蜜をあげましょう
Let's give honey to the vase,
時の中散らねったこと忘れてた
I'd forgotten things scattered in time.
さあ だだだだだまれ黙って前よ
Now, shut up, shut up, look forward!
言えないね そんな強い言葉は
I can't say such strong words,
少しだけ静かにして欲しいね ああ 私達大望へ
I want you to be a little quiet, ah, toward our grand ambition.
今と未来 見たかったはずなのに
Though we should have wanted to see the present and future,
世界 てててててぶくややや 見えるその日まで
until the day we can see it across the world,
とことことことこ ええええ これの断わりよよよよ
toko-toko-toko-toko, eeee, refusing this, yo-yo-yo,
今はせせせせ 服ざざざざ あなたの街中
now, uniform, za-za-za-za, in your town,
形作るバテンさあ だだだだだまれ黙って前よ
shaping batten, now shut up, shut up, look forward!
果たすその日まで レルレルレ獄 やややや
Until the day we achieve it, rel-rel-re hell, ya-ya-ya,
あなたの周りも よよよよ 理解 せせせせ制服 あれあれあれ
and around you too, yo-yo-yo, understand, uniform, ah-ah-ah,
約束の地まで
to the promised land.
さあ掲げよ バテン バテン てててててぶく 浸ったら見て 手の平を合わせましょう
Now raise it up, batten, batten, gloves... if you're immersed, let's clap our hands.
お待たせいたしました！
Thank you for waiting!
はい、ということで引き続きゲストパートをお送りしてまいりましたが、
Yes, so we've been continuing to bring you the guest part,
なんと、もう一人MCに呼びたいと思います！
and we'd like to invite one more person as an MC!
誰だ誰だ誰だ！？ とわ先輩！
Who could it be, who could it be?! Towa-senpai!
はい！イェイイェイイェイ！
Hi! Yay, yay, yay!
来てくれてありがとうございます！
Thank you for coming!
いやーこちらこそ！
Well, thanks for having me!
ちょっとせっかくなんで自己紹介していただいてもいいですか？
Since we have the chance, could you introduce yourself?
はい！オッケー！ホロライブ4期生の… あれ？
Okay! Hololive 4th gen... Wait, what?
こよぴーがいないから言えないんだ。こよぴー！
I can't say it because Koyopii isn't here. Koyopii!
はい、皆さん、改めてホロライブの女幹部改め、ルイと申します！
Yes everyone, once again, I'm the female commander of Hololive, newly named Lui!
リリカのお誕生日、おめでとう！
Ririka, happy birthday!
おめでとうございます！ めっちゃ嬉しい！
Congratulations! I'm so happy!
喜びの舞
A dance of joy—
呼んでくれて嬉しいよ、お誕生日にさ。
I'm so glad you invited me to your birthday.
ありがとうございますもう。ルイね、もう、トワ先輩も、もうすごくリリカに優しくしてくれる。
Thank you so much. Lui, and Towa-senpai too, are both so kind to Ririka.
もうリリカ的には姉御的な存在なので。もう頭上がんないす、頭上がんないす。
To Ririka, you're like older sisters. I can't look you in the eye, I really can't.
そういう時はね、謙遜しないんだね。
At times like that, you don't stay humble, huh?
そう、もう、そう、そう。
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
だから、もうめっちゃ嬉しいです。
So, I'm just so happy.
やばい、このキラキラについていけない。キラキラキラキラキラキラキラキラ。
Oh no, I can't keep up with this sparkle. Sparkle sparkle...
ちなみにどうですか？
By the way, how is it?
かの遊園地なんです！
It's an amusement park!
めっちゃいい！
Super nice!
最高なの！いいね！
It's the best! Awesome!
いいでしょ？ジェットコースターもあるんだよ。
Right? There's even a roller coaster.
乗ってみたい！あとで乗ろうよ。
I wanna ride it! Let's ride it later.
結構すごいスピードだよ。
It goes pretty fast, you know.
ちゃんと乗れるようになってるんでぜひ！
It's made so you can definitely ride it!
じゃああとで一緒に乗ろうよ！
Then let's ride it together later!
店も用意してるのでこっちに来てね！
We've also prepared a shop over here!
なんの店？こっちです！こっちこっち！
What kind of shop? Over here!
こっちです！こっちこっち！わあ！すごい！
Over here! This way, this way! Wow!
なんとお店もありますよ！すごい！すごい！
There's even a shop here! Amazing!
風船も付いてるんだ！
It comes with balloons too!
ちょっとこの店でソフトクリーム食べれるんで...
You can eat soft serve at this shop, so...
先輩たちにいつもお世話になってる先輩たちに！
We'll treat our seniors who always help us!
やったー！もちろんデス！
Yay! Of course!
じゃあいただきます！いただきます！
It's time to eat!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
よかったら食べてください！いただきます！
Enjoy your ice cream!
ありがとう、うまいわ！おいしい！
Thank you, it's delicious!
サンキュー！あまーい！
Thank you so much! Sweet!
めちゃくちゃ濃厚でうまいな！
It's super rich and delicious!
よくアイス食べる？食べる！好き！
Do you usually eat soft serve?
ミルクが好きなんだよ。ミルクうまいよね。
I love milk-flavored ice cream.
私もこのワッフルコーン大好きでよく食べるよ。
I love waffle cones too!
実はあんまりアイス食べないんだけど...
I don't usually eat ice cream much, but...
でも氷が好き！氷！
I love ice!
クリーム系だけど今日ね。
Mostly cream-based today, though.
クリームしかざるがなかったんだもん！
There's only cream left!
本当にありがとうございます！
Thank you so much for today!
ライブステージも紹介させてください！
Let me introduce the live stage too!
今回はなんと、遊園地ステージとなっております！
This time it's an amusement park stage!
観覧車がすごい綺麗だし！
The Ferris wheel is so pretty!
ジェットコースターが今走って！
The roller coaster is running right now!
すっごい速い！マジ速い！
It's so fast!
ドキドキしちゃう、もしかしたら眩暈しちゃうかも。
You might even get dizzy if you ride it.
いろいろ乗れるのでよかったら満喫していってね！
You can ride various things, so please enjoy!
いいですか？二人乗ってね！
Are you two going to ride it?
ライブ見てるよこうやって。
We're watching the live stream like this!
どこかに行っちゃうかもしれない！
We might end up somewhere far away!
今日お二人に来ていただいてめちゃくちゃ嬉しくて！
We're so happy you two came today!
同時視聴をさせていただいたんですけど！
We did a simultaneous live broadcast!
その時にファクト聞いて！
We listened to 'Fact' at that time!
やべえ！めっちゃかっけえ！
It was so cool!
あんな風に歌えるようになりたい！踊れるようになりたい！
I wanted to sing and dance like that too!
こんなに興奮してくれたの！マジでこれ！
We were so excited!
一緒に歌って踊ってもらえて本当に嬉しいです！
I'm so glad we could sing and dance together!
リリカとトワはオーバーロードを歌って踊らせていただきました！
Ririka and Towa sang 'Overdose'!
オーバーロードもめちゃくちゃ好きな曲で！
I love 'Overdose' so much!
一緒に歌いたいね、いつかって言ってたのが！
I always said I wanted to sing it with you!
今回こうやって夢がかなってもめちゃくちゃ嬉しいです！
I'm so happy it came true today!
大人の色気ちゃんと出せてましたか？
Did we show our mature charm?
出せてましたよ！素晴らしかったです！
We did! It was wonderful!
大人の色気を見せていきましたから！
We showed our mature charm!
いかがだったでしょうか？
How was it?
本当にありがとうございます！嬉しい！
Thank you so much, we're so happy!
このあともあるので楽しんでね！
Ririka has more coming up, so please look forward to it!
二人からがんばれのエールを送りたいです！
Let's send our cheers to both of them!
二人でお礼の挨拶をしましょうか！
Let's express our gratitude too!
せーの！がんばれー！
Ready, set, do your best!
リリカー！
Ririka!
goin' goin' my way もうほっといて
Goin' goin' my way, just leave me alone
Goin' goin' my way もう ほっといて
止められない熱 身任せて
I can't stop this fever, just leave it to me
I know who I am, ayy
ブランディングにはあかんべ
Sticking my tongue out at branding
今は完全無視よ 何でもアリの greedy style
Now I'm totally ignoring it, anything goes greedy style
ダサいヤッカイも興味ないの
Not interested in cheesy jealousy either
ありのままでいたい
I just want to be myself
Goin' goin' my way もう ほっといて
Goin' goin' my way, just leave me alone
止められない熱 身任せて
I can't stop this fever, just leave it to me
こりごりだ ruleは break it down
I'm fed up, the rule is to break it down
我慢出来ない let me free
I can't take it anymore, let me free
we are special でしょ？ 揺るがないpride
We are special, right? Unwavering pride
それだけでいいの たらればだらけのlowな日々を break it down
That's all I need. Those low days full of "what-ifs", break it down
break it we are special でしょ？
break it... We are special, right?
誰に言われても私は歌うよ アンフェアばかりのセカイなど
No matter what anyone says, I will sing in this unfair world
break it down, break it ススメ アンフェアばかりのセカイなど
Break it down, go, break it down
break it down, break it ススメ
i just don't care about you!
ハイテクなメイクやファッションも
High-tech makeup and fashion too
self-loveには敵わないよ
Can't beat self-love
この身と心 誰のものでもないでしょ
This body and heart, they don't belong to anyone
いい加減に大人だよね…？
It's about time, you're an adult, right...?
Inilah aku apa adanya, tidak sempurna, tapi sepenuhnya diriku
This is who I am, not perfect, but fully myself
でも今は楽しいよ ありのままでいられるから！
But I'm happy now, because I can be myself!
Goin' goin' my way もう ほっといて
Goin' goin' my way, just leave me alone
止められない熱 身任せて
I can't stop this fever, just leave it to me
こりごりだ ruleは break it down
I'm fed up, the rule is to break it down
我慢出来ない let me free
I can't take it anymore, let me free
we are special でしょ？ 揺るがないpride
We are special, right? Unwavering pride
それだけでいいの たらればだらけのlowな日々を break it down
That's all I need. Those low days full of "what-ifs", break it down
break it we are special でしょ？
break it... We are special, right?
誰に言われても私は歌うよ アンフェアばかりのセカイなど
No matter what anyone says, I will sing in this unfair world
break it down, break it ススメ
Break it down, go, break it down
can't break me down, breaking me
break it down, break it down
break it down, break it ススメ
Break it down, go, break it down
break it down, break it down
Goin' goin' my way もう ほっといて
Goin' goin' my way, just leave me alone
止められない熱 身任せて
I can't stop this fever, just leave it to me
こりごりだ ruleは break it down
I'm fed up, the rule is to break it down
我慢出来ない let me free
I can't take it anymore, let me free
次の曲は SUPER DUPER!
The next song is SUPER DUPER!
Ready to go? Let's go!
めくるめく好奇心は羅針盤
A dizzying curiosity is my compass
行く末 噛み締めても知らぬ場所
Even if I savor the future, it's a place I don't know
混じり気のない情熱が
Pure, unadulterated passion
澄ますした空を跨いだどこ
Straddled across the clear sky somewhere
寝付きの悪い夜も程遠い話と
Restless nights feel like a distant story
いつも目まぐるしい時代も全部
And this dizzying era, all of it
忘却の彼方へ笑い飛ばそう
Let's laugh away into oblivion
Give me 出来得る限り今すぐ!
Give me whatever I can right now!
SUPER DUPER おもとく重力のシャンデリア
SUPER DUPER, unravelling the chandelier of gravity
弾け暮れるまで踊ろうよ 誰が何と言おうと
Let's dance until we burst out, no matter what anyone says
気にしない見果てぬ怪鳥
Not caring about the unreachable strange bird
外側の趣味だけ美しい声を響かせて
Let only the outer taste resonate with a beautiful voice
Yay, yay, yay, yay, yay, yay, oh, oh!
うつむいた世界を変えてみせよ
Show me you can change this downcast world!
彷徨う こんなんじゃもう自ずと消す逆転
Wandering like this, naturally erasing the reversal
とうとい的決める 激熱大作戦
Precious targets, a super heated grand strategy
転生してももう一度ここにカムバック
Even if I reincarnate, I'll make a comeback right here
人生そのものがセンセーショナルな漫画
Life itself is a sensational manga
ビギナーから一歩羽ばたいてゴリジナリ
Fluttering a step away from a beginner to originality
一番目指す走り出す天才が天才
Aiming for the number one, running out genius is a genius
しまったお揺るがすポウヨさは打ち落としたって問題ない
No problem even if you shoot down the shaking power
接ぎ木いて胸を僕愛してやまないもの 歌うことが子ども知らないまま
Grafting and loving my chest, not knowing singing like a child
そういっそ決着は付いてるよ
Yes, the outcome is already decided
Give me the givin' la-bi-ra-i-na!
SUPER DUPER おもとく重力のシャンデリア 弾け暮れるまで踊ろうよ 誰が何と言おうと気にしなリーミ
SUPER DUPER, unravelling the chandelier of gravity...
yeah yeah！ yeah yeah！
Yeah, yeah! Yeah, yeah!
yeah yeah！ ah-ah
Yeah, yeah! Ah-ah!
yeah yeah！ yeah yeah！
Yeah, yeah! Yeah, yeah!
めくるめく好奇心は森羅万象　行く末神さえも知らない場所
Curiosity spinning endlessly, not even knowing where it leads.
混ざり気のない情熱が澄ましいた空虚を逆撫でたところ
Unmixed passion turning over a serene vacuum.
寝付きの悪い夜も途方もないバッドニュースも 目まぐるしい時代も全部忘れの彼方へ笑い飛ばそう
Let's laugh away troublesome nights and endless bad news into the distance.
gimme that gimme that beat right now！
Gimme that beat right now!
super duper オートチューンのshangri-laで
In a super duper autotuned Shangri-La,
日が暮れるまで踊ろうよ　誰が何と言おうと気にしない
Let's dance until the sun goes down, no matter what anyone says.
リミッター解除　そう、ただ楽しむだけ 美しい声を響かせて
No limits, just having fun, letting a beautiful voice ring out!
yeah yeah！ yeah yeah！ yeah yeah！ ah-ah ah-ah
Yeah, yeah! Yeah, yeah! Yeah, yeah! Ah-ah!
俯いた世界を変えてみせよう
Let's try changing the world we look down upon!
yeah yeah！ yeah yeah！ yeah yeah！
Yeah, yeah! Yeah, yeah! Yeah, yeah!
super duper
功が奏して満を期して形勢逆転
Merit playing out, anticipating the full force, turning the tables,
たった一手決める激アツ確変
A single decisive move, a guaranteed hype moment!
転生してももう一度ここにcome back
Reincarnate and come back here once more.
人生そのものがセンセーショナルな漫画
Life itself is a sensational manga,
ビギナーから一躍羽ばたいていくオリジナル
Soaring from a beginner to an original.
一番目指し走り出す　でも地に足つけるジーニアス
Aiming for number one, but keeping our feet on the ground as geniuses.
巷を揺るがすボヤ騒ぎ　浮き足立ったって問題ない
A buzzing rumor shaking the town, floating is no problem!
ざらついた胸の奥　愛してやまないもの
Deep in our restless hearts, we love it unconditionally,
疑うことも知らないまま　添い遂げる覚悟はできているよ
Without even knowing doubt, we have the resolve to see it through.
gimme that gimme that beat right now！
Gimme that beat right now!
というわけで！ReGLOSSでSUPER DUPERをお送りしました！
And so, ReGLOSS is here to bring you Super Duper!
みんな来てくれてるね！やったー！やったー！やったー！やったー！
Everyone came, didn't they? Yay! Yay! Yay! Yay!
さっきもやったんだけどもう一回やってもいい？
We already did this a bit ago, but can we do it again?
あ！うん！いつもできます！
Of course! We can always do it.
リザートップ！私たちはReGLOSS！
ReaZort! We are ReGLOSS!
せっかくだからちょっとみんなに自己紹介してほしくて。じゃあ、かなでから！
Since this is our chance, let's have everyone introduce themselves! Ririka, go ahead!
はい！えっと、一条莉リカの恋人！踊ろうぜ、かなでだよ！
Hi! Um... I'm Ichijo Ririka's lover! Let's party, Kanade!
え！いつの間に恋人だったんだ！
Wait, you were a lover?
あ！りりか大好きだよ！
Ririka, I love you so much!
そして…
And then...
ええ、一条莉リカのペットじゃん！
Um, I'm Ichijo Ririka's pet!
わんわんわんわん！
Woof woof woof!
そして？
And then?
えーっと、一条莉リカの、えっと、配信デスクの上のタンプラを置く、あの、ポスターみたいなやつ自分寺ですの！
Uh, I'm Ichijo Ririka's... desk lamp? Poster-like thing in her room?
何それ一体！ペットじゃねえ！ペットじゃねえじゃん！
What on earth is that?! That's not a pet!
ずっと思ってた、そういうことか！
Oh, so that's what it was.
やったー！
Yay!
みんな来てくれてマジでありがとね！来てくれて嬉しい！
Everyone who came, seriously, thank you so much!
誕生日だっけ？なんの誕生日だっけ？
Happy birthday! Wait, whose birthday was it again?
違う、誕生日だの？
Wait, whose birthday was it?
そうです。莉リカ、お誕生日になりました。おめでとうみんな！誕生日おめでとう！
That's right! Ririka, happy birthday!
なんか誕生日って、いいな。毎日誕生日がいい！
You know, birthdays are great. Everyday birthdays would be great.
毎日誕生日だったら、毎日年取ることになるけど。
If every day was your birthday, you'd age a year every day though!
じゃあ、この話は終わりということで！
Okay, let's drop that subject!
おいといてね！
Just ignore that!
はい、じゃあここからはね、ちょっと告知をさせていただきたいなと。あ、待って、あります！告知！
Right, from here we'd like to make some announcements. Wait, there's more?
もしや！一条莉リカ誕生日記念2025グッズが出でるってこと？！
Could it be... Ichijo Ririka Birthday Celebration 2025 Goods are out?!
やったーー！じゃあこちらをご覧ください！
Yay! So let's take a look at these!
じゃじゃーん！かわいい！これのりりか！
Ta-da! So cute! Oh, it's Ririka!
かわいい！チュキチュキチュキ！エクティや！
So cute! Chuki chuki chuki! Equity!
いや、こちらはね、もう初めてのサンタさんのグッズということで、もうもりだくさんのグッズになっております！
This is, well, our very first Santa-themed merch, so it's packed with tons of items!
めっちゃいい！で、今回はですね、イラストはトマリ先生に描いていただきました。本当にありがとうございます！
So good! And this time, the illustration was drawn by Tomari-sensei! Thank you so much!
かわいい！かわいくて美しくて最高だよね！
So cute, cute! It's so cute, beautiful, and the best, right?
じゃあちょっと詳細も見ていきたいと思います。まずはこちら！
Now let's take a look at the details. First is this!
いぇーい！出た出た。みんな画角に入ってね！
Yay! There it is, everyone, look closely!
りりかの大きすぎすて。
Ririka's goods are way too big!
えー、まずはアクリルスマホスタンドです！
So first is the acrylic smartphone stand!
今回ね、オリジナル衣装で歌って踊ってるりりかの描き下ろしイラスト
This features an original outfit illustration of Ririka singing and dancing, drawn by Tomari-sensei!
してもらいました！でもめちゃくちゃ本当に可愛いし
It's made for you! It's super, truly cute,
もうね、アクリルスマホスタンドなので、スマホの上に置けるということ、
And since it's an acrylic smartphone stand, you can put your phone on top of it,
つまりずっと一緒にいられるということ！いぇーい！
Meaning you can stay together with me forever! Yay!
大事に使ってください。そして続いてはこちら！
Please take good care of it! And next is this!
じゃん！かわいい！
Ta-da! Cute!
かわいい！ランダムラバーストラップ！
The random rubber strap!
ま、やっぱりね、リカ、あのオタクなので自分自身も、うーん何にしようかなって考えたときに
Well, since Ririka is an otaku herself, when I thought about what I'd want,
ラバーストラップ欲しすぎ！
I want rubber straps way too much!
欲しすぎ！可愛すぎ！
So cute! Too cute!
今回ね、あのうえからエク先生に4種類のリカを書き下ろしていただきました！
This time, Kamikura Eku-sensei drew four different versions of Ririka for us!
めちゃくちゃ可愛い！ありがとうございます！
They're super cute! Thank you so much!
あく、あくえくれいじょなの？
Are these the "Aku-Kurei-jo" versions?
そうだよ、悪役令嬢のリカもいます！
That's right, there are also "Aku-yaku-Rei-jo" versions of Ririka!
うわあ！りりかさま！りりかさま！りりかさま！
Yay! Ririka-sama! Ririka-sama!
そう、リリー様！リリー様！リリー様ですわ！
Right, Lily-sama! Lily-sama!
リリー様ですわ！オオタカ出てきた、リリー様だ。リリー様だっけ？
Lily-sama is... wait, did you just make that up?
ねえ、無理しました今。
Yeah, I forced that one!
で、こちらは、えっと、ランダムで1種類封入されております。
And this one will be randomly included
with one out of four types.
おお！
Wow!
そして、続いてはこちら！
And next is this!
ウニペンケース！
The Uni pen case!
え、かわいい！
Ah, so cute!
めっちゃいいでしょこれ、もう。
Isn't this great?
めっちゃいい。
So good.
ふわふわでね、もうめちゃくちゃかわいいもう。
It's super fluffy and just insanely cute.
お腹しゃくれてる？
Is its belly jutting out?
お腹じゃなくて背中ね背中！
Not the belly, the back, the back!
背中は空いてますが、まあ、内臓がペンみたいな感じでね。
The back opens up, and the inside is like a pen.
なるほどね。
I see.
なるほど！
I see!
かわいがってあげてください。
Please treat it with love.
普段使いできるのでぜひぜひ使ってください。
You can use it everyday, so please use it!
かわいい！
Cute!
続いてはこちら！
Next is this!
なんと、限界飯プレートが出ます！
And the Extreme Meal Plate is coming out!
めっちゃかわいい！
So cute!
あ、コメヤ！すごくない！？
Ah, Comeya! Isn't that amazing!?
そう、これね、あの、お米が敷いてあるようなイラストのプレートなので、
This plate has an illustration as if rice is spread out,
もうこの上にね、国債を乗せれば簡単にお手軽に限界飯が作れるという優れものになっております！
so you can easily make an extreme meal!
めっちゃいいじゃん！
That's so great!
かわいい！
Cute!
イェーイ！
Yay!
そして、ウニもちらっと書いてある。
And Uni is also drawn faintly on it.
そう、ウニもいますよ。
That's right, Uni is there too.
かわいい！
Cute!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
じゃ、続いてはこちら！
Then, next is this!
まあね、ボイスもやろうかなっていうことで！
Well, we're also going to do voice packs!
今回、みんな待望のASMRボイス収録しております！
We've recorded everyone's long-awaited ASMR voice!
やったー！
Yay!
1個目は、莉々華の部屋で一緒にゲーム！
The first is playing games in Ririka's room!
で、まあ、莉々華のね、おうちで、隣で、なんか一緒にゲームをしてるかのようなラブラブボイスとなっておりますので、よろしくお願いします！
It's a lovey-dovey voice like you're playing games together!
いいねー！
Sounds great!
買うしかない！聴くしかない！
Gotta buy it! Gotta listen!
そして、なんとですね、フルセットの購入特典もございます！こちらです！じゃん！
And there's also a full-set purchase bonus! Here it is!
まずは、直筆サインがついてきまーす！
First off, it comes with an autograph!
で、こちらはですね、もう、莉々華限定とかじゃなくて、買ってくださった方には全員におつけしたいと思っているので、ぜひいっぱいいっぱい購入してもらえると嬉しいです。ポストカードに直筆サインをつけてお渡しします。
I want to give it to everyone who buys it, so please buy lots.
で、もう一つが、さっきASMR 1個目はって言ったんですけど、2個目がこちらで、
And the second ASMR is...
「あなたの誕生日をお祝い」ということで、
"Celebrating your birthday,"
今回ね、まあ、今日は莉々華の誕生日をみんなにこうやってお祝いしてもらってるわけですけど、
Today everyone is celebrating Ririka's birthday,
莉々華もみんなの誕生日をお祝いしたいと思って、今回準備しました！ぜひ自分の誕生日に聞いてください！
so I prepared this to celebrate everyone's birthdays too!
はい、じゃあ改めて、フルセットはこちらとなります！
Yes, so once again, here is the full set!
じゃーん！いや、なんて豪華なんだ！
Ta-da! Oh, how luxurious!
あんまりにもいっぱいありすぎて、ねえ、もう絶対に買ってください！絶対に絶対によろしくお願いします！
There's so much, please definitely buy it!
そしてさらに、タレントプレミアムグッズのフルセット特典として、
And as a full-set bonus for the premium goods,
去年から発売されているホロライブオフィシャルカードゲームで、なんと使用できるカードが1枚ついてきまーす！
it comes with a usable card for the Hololive Card Game!
カードはホロライブプロダクションオフィシャルショップでご購入された方のみが対象となります。
Cards are only for purchases from the Official Shop.
特典につくのは、推しをアピールできるキーカード、「推しホロメン」のカードです！
The bonus is an "Oshi Holomember" card!
カードの詳細や遊び方などについてはホームページにてご確認ください。
Please check the homepage for details.
なんと、実はまだお知らせがあるんです！
Actually, there's still an announcement!
こちらをご覧ください！じゃーん！
Please look at this! Ta-da!
おお、出た！
Oh, it's out!
よしよしよし、一條莉々華のLINEスタンプの制作が決定しました！
Ichijou Ririka LINE stamps will be produced!
詳細物は後日公開となりますので、ご確認のほどよろしくお願いします。めっちゃ可愛くない？
Details will be announced later. Isn't it super cute?
やばすぎでしょ！いっぱい使ってください！
It's too crazy! Please use them a lot!
以上、一條莉々華生誕祭記念ライブのグッズ情報でした！みんなに買っていただけるととても嬉しいです！
That was the merch info for the birthday live!
改めてにはなるんですけど、もう本当にこうやってね、今回ライブ、生誕ライブ無いつやる事ができて、もうめちゃくちゃ嬉しい気持ちでいっぱいです。たくさんの応援コメント、もう常日頃からね、莉々華にいっぱいついて、届いております。
I'm so filled with joy to be able to hold this birthday live.
みんなが応援してくれたおかげで、また莉々華ダンス頑張れた！歌も頑張れた！
Thanks to your support, I could do my best at dancing and singing!
これからもたくさんたくさんみんなといろんな景色見れるように頑張りますので、よろしくお願いします！
I'll do my best so we can see many more views together!
でさ、あれ？メグロススどこいった？
And hey, where did Megross go?
消えた！？
It disappeared!?
え！？なんで！？どこ！？
Eh!? Why!? Where!?
莉々華、こっちだよ！
Ririka, over here!
キャッキャ、ガタゴト！
Yay, rattle rattle!
うわあ、メグロス、いつの間にメリーゴーランドに乗ってたの！
Wow, Megross, when did you get on the merry-go-round?!
ええ、楽しそう！
Wow, looks fun!
白馬の王子様みたいになってるじゃん、班長。
You look like a prince on a white horse, squad leader.
ちょうどだ、ちょうどだ！
Perfect timing!
ほからっぽから。
Empty empty.
いいなー。莉々華も乗りたい気持ちはいっぱいあるんだけどさ、この後まだアンコールライブもあるから。
Ririka also wants to ride, but we have an encore live after this.
ごめんね、これ3人用なんだ。
Sorry, this is for three people.
いやいやいや、こんなに席あったのに、3人用だったんだこれ！そうなの、二人になると止んじゃう。止んじゃう重さで！
Even though there were so many seats, it was for three people!
莉々華の、莉々華の体重のせいで、止まっちゃった！
Because of Ririka's weight, it stopped!
まあ、なんか言ってるけれどね。
Well, she's saying all that, but...
この後、莉々華メングロスでのアンコールライブがありまーす！おお、がんばれー！
After this, there will be an encore live by Ririka and Megloss!
アンコールライブでは、ホロライブのあの曲やあの曲を歌っちゃおう！
At the encore live, let's sing songs like that!
思ってるので楽しんでもらえると嬉しいです！
I hope you all enjoy it!
残ってくれて嬉しい！
I'm so glad you stayed!
じゃあみんな今日来てくれて本当にありがとうね！
So everyone, thank you so much for coming today!
この後もゆっくり楽しんでね！バイバイ！
Enjoy the rest of the time at your own pace! Bye-bye!
バイバイ！
Bye-bye!
大スキな秘書のみんなへ
苦手だった歌やダンスをがんばりたい！って思えるようになったのはみんなのおかげだよ。
To all my beloved secretaries...
Wanting to try harder at singing and dancing was all thanks to you.
これからもずっとそばで応援してくれる？
変わらない毎日と新しいチャレンジを一緒に…✨
Will you keep supporting me by my side?
Sharing unchanging days and new challenges together...
ホロライブに入れてよかった！！
I'm so glad I joined Hololive!!